<interview_brief phase="4">
  <summary>39 should-improve items found across L2 (10), L3 (16), L4 (13) for Phase 4 deliverable.</summary>

  <topic_group source="L2 -- Domain Expert (Senior Database Architect / Backend Lead)">
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-1">
      <context>From deliverable: "handicap: INTEGER | | Golf handicap (1-36 typically). Used for course selection and tee time requests." The word "typically" indicates uncertainty, and no CHECK constraint or validation rule is specified.</context>
      <gap>The `handicap` field is INTEGER but provides no constraint documentation on valid range, making it unclear if negative values, 0, or >36 are allowed, creating data quality risk.</gap>
      <question>Add CHECK constraint to the schema: `CHECK (handicap IS NULL OR (handicap >= 0 AND handicap <= 36))`. If handicaps outside this range are possible (e.g., elite players with negative handicaps), adjust the constraint and document the business rule in the Data Dictionary.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-2">
      <context>From deliverable: "role: TEXT | NOT NULL, DEFAULT 'member' | User's role determining what they can see/do: 'owner' (Rafael), 'operations' (Lucia), 'finance', 'support', 'member'. Controls UI features and API permissions." No CHECK constraint or foreign key to a roles table.</context>
      <gap>The `role` field is a plain TEXT enum but does not enforce role membership (e.g., how is the set of valid roles ['owner', 'operations', 'finance', 'support', 'member'] enforced?). This creates risk of data corruption via invalid roles.</gap>
      <question>Either (1) add CHECK constraint: `CHECK (role IN ('owner', 'operations', 'finance', 'support', 'member'))`, or (2) create a `roles` lookup table (`id, role_name, permissions_json`) and add `role_id UUID REFERENCES roles(id)` to users. Option (1) is sufficient for MVP; option (2) is more flexible for Expansion Phase if role definitions need to be operator-specific. Document the choice in Phase 5 schema DDL.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-3">
      <context>From Phase 4 outputs template: "**3. RLS Policy Document** — Row Level Security policies for every table. For each table: the select, insert, update, and delete policies, expressed as rules tied to the authenticated user's role and organization." But the deliverable integrates RLS into the security section without a dedicated policy reference document.</context>
      <gap>The section promises "RLS Policy Document" as a distinct deliverable but the content is embedded in Part 5 (Security Model) with no separate, dedicated RLS policy reference that Phase 5 developers can use directly to implement policies.</gap>
      <question>Create Appendix D (RLS Policy Specification) listing every RLS policy for every table in the format: Table Name | Policy Name | Action (SELECT/INSERT/UPDATE/DELETE) | Rule (in SQL) | Role-Based Restrictions. This will serve as the reference for Phase 5 implementation and ensure no policy is overlooked.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-4">
      <context>From deliverable: "created_by_user_id: UUID | REFERENCES users(id) | Which team member created this booking (usually system, but can be Rafael if manually entered)" with no NOT NULL constraint and no mention of handling if the user is deleted.</context>
      <gap>The `created_by_user_id` field can be NULL or reference a user who is later deleted/soft-deleted, making audit trail incomplete. The design does not enforce immutability of the creator reference.</gap>
      <question>Either (1) add NOT NULL constraint and require a 'system' or 'admin' user record that is never deleted, OR (2) denormalize by storing user_email in addition to user_id so the creator's name is preserved even if the user record is deleted. Document the chosen approach in Phase 5; include this in audit trail testing (Phase 7).</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-5">
      <context>From deliverable: "shareable_link_uuid: UUID | UNIQUE | Unique, anonymous URL token for sharing itinerary with secondary golfers (no login required). They visit: https://oceangolf.com/itinerary/[uuid]." No mention of link rotation or regeneration mechanism.</context>
      <gap>The `shareable_link_uuid` is UNIQUE, but there is no documented mechanism to regenerate/rotate this link if it is leaked or if the itinerary is updated, creating potential security risk.</gap>
      <question>Add column `shareable_link_rotated_at TIMESTAMP WITH TIME ZONE | NULL` and document in Data Dictionary that (1) original link is valid until shareable_link_expires_at, (2) if client requests a new link (e.g., to revoke secondary access), a new UUID is generated and old UUID becomes invalid, (3) the old UUID is retained in a audit table for compliance. Implement link rotation in Phase 5.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-6">
      <context>From deliverable: "commission_type: TEXT | DEFAULT 'percent' | 'percent' (15% of green fee) or 'flat' ($150 per booking). Determines how to calculate costs." But there is no constraint linking commission_type to commission_rate_percent validation.</context>
      <gap>The `commission_type` field is ENUM ('percent', 'flat') but the schema does not enforce that commission_rate_percent is NULL when commission_type = 'flat', creating data quality ambiguity.</gap>
      <question>Add CHECK constraint: `CHECK ((commission_type = 'percent' AND commission_rate_percent IS NOT NULL) OR (commission_type = 'flat' AND commission_rate_percent IS NULL))` OR add separate column `commission_rate_flat_cents INTEGER` to explicitly distinguish the two models and ensure no ambiguity. Document the chosen approach in Phase 5.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-7">
      <context>From deliverable: "cost_type: TEXT | NOT NULL | What kind of cost: 'green_fee', 'commission', 'villa_nightly', 'meal_total', 'driver_fee', 'activity_fee', etc." The "etc." indicates an open set, but no validation mechanism is defined.</context>
      <gap>The `cost_type` field allows any TEXT value without enum constraints (examples: 'green_fee', 'commission', 'villa_nightly', etc.), but no exhaustive list of valid cost types is provided, creating risk of data quality inconsistency (e.g., 'green_fee' vs. 'greenfee' vs. 'course_green_fee').</gap>
      <question>Either (1) create a `cost_types` lookup table with all valid cost_type values and add `cost_type_id UUID REFERENCES cost_types(id)`, OR (2) add CHECK constraint to costs table: `CHECK (cost_type IN ('green_fee', 'commission', 'villa_nightly', 'meal_total', 'driver_fee', 'activity_fee', ...))` with exhaustive list. Document the chosen approach and the full list of valid cost_type values in the Data Dictionary for Phase 5.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-4-L2-8">
      <context>From deliverable: "is_demo_tenant: BOOLEAN | DEFAULT FALSE | TRUE if this is demo data (isolated, reset weekly). FALSE for production." The phrase "reset weekly" is mentioned in template behavioral rules but not in the schema or operational procedures.</context>
      <gap>The `is_demo_tenant` boolean is documented as supporting demo data isolation, but there is no documented retention/reset procedure for demo data (e.g., how often is demo data reset? what is the retention period?), making the design incomplete for operational use.</gap>
      <question>Document in Phase 8 Operations: (1) automated job that resets demo tenant data every Sunday 00:00 UTC, (2) what "reset" means (truncate all tables with operator_id = 'demo_operator', re-seed with fixture data from version control), (3) retention of demo data during the week for testing, (4) exclusion of demo data from analytics/reporting. Include backup and recovery procedures for demo data.</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

</interview_brief>