<interview_brief phase="6c">
  <summary>20 should-improve items found across L2 (5), L3 (7), L4 (8) for Phase 6c deliverable.</summary>

  <topic_group source="L2 -- Domain Expert (Design Director / Principal Designer)">
    <topic id="SI-6c-L2-1">
      <context>Section 2.10 example: "Invalid phone number for Carlos — Check contact info" is specific (good) but phrased as "Check contact info" (imperative) rather than in the "honest, respectful" voice that acknowledges "This is a data issue in our system" vs. "You entered it wrong." Section 1.2 voice definition states: "Blame the right culprit" with example "Network error" not "You tried to send without connection."</context>
      <gap>Microcopy examples are written in first-person narrative context (Lucia performs action, sees toast) but some error message examples blame the user ("Group size must be 1-4 golfers") where they should use voice that blames the right culprit per Section 1.2 voice definition ("Honest, not euphemistic").</gap>
      <question>Audit all error messages in Sections 2.1-2.10 for voice consistency. Where errors are data-quality or system issues (invalid phone stored in system), frame as "System issue: [field] in our database appears invalid" rather than "Check contact info" (which sounds like Lucia's fault). Verify all 100+ phrases against the voice definition in Section 1.2 before Phase 7 implementation to ensure consistency.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-6c-L2-2">
      <context>Section 4.5 states: "Founder's Implementation Question: 'Would a fade feel smoother...'" and D7 resolution proposes 150ms. Then Section 4.6 notes "Pending 2-day Lucia review: During the 2-day validation cycle, Lucia should confirm 150ms feels appropriate..." This indicates 150ms is a proposal pending validation, not locked approval.</context>
      <gap>Dark mode color transition timing specification (150ms ease-out) is presented as founder-approved, but the approval appears to be inferred from founder feedback rather than explicitly stated as locked. Template requires founder approval of timing, and founder's original question ("Would a fade feel smoother, or would that just feel slow?") suggests this was a trade-off decision, not a finalized spec.</gap>
      <question>Update Section 4.5 to clarify decision status: (1) If founder has explicitly approved 150ms, quote the approval. (2) If timing is pending Lucia's operational feedback, move to "PENDING VALIDATION" section and note that Phase 7 should not hard-code timing until confirmed. Currently it's ambiguous whether 150ms is a founder decision or a designer proposal.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-6c-L2-3">
      <context>Section 12 states: "Updated items: brief highlight flash (1 second accent background fade)." D7 transition scale (from Section 1 context) uses: 100-150ms (micro), 200-250ms (state transitions), 250-350ms (page transitions), 400-600ms (complex). 1 second (1000ms) is not on this scale. Template Section 12 says "All new timing values... must reference the existing duration scale from Phase 6A. If a new duration is needed... add it to the duration scale rather than using an ad-hoc value."</context>
      <gap>Real-time update rendering pattern specifies "highlight flash (1 second accent background fade)" for updated items, but this animation timing is not mapped to D7 transition/animation tokens, creating a discrepancy with design system discipline (D7 Section 6: "All visual properties must reference design tokens, never hardcoded values").</gap>
      <question>Either (1) update the highlight flash to use an existing D7 transition duration (e.g., 200-250ms state transition timing is appropriate for item highlight), OR (2) add a new "highlight flash" duration (1000ms) to D7's transition/animation scale with explicit token name (e.g., `--duration-highlight-flash: 1000ms`) and document in D7 Section 1 so Phase 7 references the token rather than hard-coding 1 second.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-6c-L2-4">
      <context>Section 2.11A lists shortcuts including "K - Open Search (Phase 8+)" with note "Deferred to Phase 8". Template Area 12 requires: "Before proposing any `Cmd+[single key]` combination, verify against common browser defaults: Cmd+D (bookmark), Cmd+B (bold), Cmd+L (address bar)..." D7 does not show this verification step for Cmd+K.</context>
      <gap>Keyboard shortcut list is incomplete relative to template requirements. Template requires "Discoverability: '?' key opens shortcut reference modal; tooltips show shortcuts on hover. Must not conflict with browser or OS shortcuts." D7 only specifies `?` for help and does NOT verify Cmd+K/Ctrl+K for search (which appears in D8 as deferred to Phase 8) against browser defaults or document verification method.</gap>
      <question>Add a verification table in Section 2.11A documenting which shortcuts were tested against browser/OS defaults (e.g., "Cmd+K verified not reserved in Chrome/Safari/Firefox as of Feb 2026"). Include testing method/tool used. If Cmd+K is being deferred to Phase 8, note explicitly that verification will occur during Phase 8 search implementation.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-6c-L2-5">
      <context>Template Area 14 states: "Accessibility Specification: Target standard, contrast verification tables (light + dark), focus management, touch targets, screen reader requirements, keyboard navigation map, motion policy, color independence verification, testing checklist. This section feeds directly into D14." D7 Section 14 is ~200 words pointing to APPENDIX A (D14 outline) rather than containing the full specification.</context>
      <gap>Section 14 is marked as a placeholder referring to D14, but the template requires a comprehensive accessibility section in D7 itself ("This section feeds directly into D14"). D7 Section 14 is essentially a stub that says "See D14" rather than providing the accessibility specification that Phase 7 developers should reference while building.</gap>
      <question>Expand D7 Section 14 to include all accessibility requirements (contrast tables, touch targets, focus indicators, screen reader annotations) so Phase 7 developers don't need to cross-reference D14 constantly. D14 can be the detailed audit checklist, but D7 Section 14 should be the implementation reference (what colors pass contrast, which ARIA attributes are required, etc.).</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

  <topic_group source="L3 -- Downstream Consumer (Engineering Manager / Technical PM)">
    <topic id="SI-6c-L3-1">
      <context>Section 2.11A provides "Keyboard shortcut: `?` (question mark key, anywhere in app)" but doesn't specify: (1) Is there a tooltip on page load for first-time users? (2) Is there a "Learn keyboard shortcuts" link in Settings? (3) Is there a help icon in header that hints at the `?` key? The Help Modal structure is shown, but discoverability is underspecified.</context>
      <gap>The keyboard shortcuts table specifies `?` key to open Help Modal and `R` to refresh hunt list, but does not document how these shortcuts are discoverable to users who don't know they exist. The Help Modal content structure is provided, but the entry point mechanism (how does user learn the `?` key exists?) is unclear.</gap>
      <question>Add a 'Discoverability Strategy' subsection to 2.11A that explains how new users learn about keyboard shortcuts: e.g., "First-time users see a soft banner: 'Tip: Press ? for keyboard shortcuts.' Subsequent visits: tooltip on ? icon in header. Persistent: Help icon (?) in footer links to Help Modal." This bridges the gap between specification (what shortcuts exist) and UX (how users discover them).</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-6c-L3-2">
      <context>Section 4.2 specifies that 150ms transition respects `prefers-reduced-motion: reduce` (disables transitions), but Section 4.1 doesn't clarify: If a user has reduced motion enabled, and they click the dark mode toggle, does the color change happen instantly (no transition), or does some other feedback occur? Is there any visual distinction between auto dark mode toggle (system preference) vs. manual toggle when reduced motion is enabled?</context>
      <gap>Section 4.1 provides comprehensive CSS and JavaScript implementation guidance, but does not specify what happens if a user has `prefers-reduced-motion: reduce` AND tries to toggle dark mode manually. The interaction between two user preferences (reduced motion + dark mode toggle) is not documented.</gap>
      <question>Add a subsection 'Dark Mode Toggle with Reduced Motion' to Section 4.1 that specifies: "If user has `prefers-reduced-motion: reduce` enabled, dark mode toggle color change is instant (no transition). Brief 200ms toast appears: 'Dark mode [on/off]' to provide feedback that the toggle was successful." This ensures accessibility for users with vestibular disorders.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-6c-L3-3">
      <context>Section 5.2 shows CSS example: `*:focus-visible { outline: 2px solid #0052A3; }` which is correct, but the preceding text says "must have a visible focus indicator for keyboard navigation" without clarifying the CSS pseudo-class strategy. Template requirement 6 (focus indicators) expects this to be unambiguous for developers.</context>
      <gap>Section 5.2 specifies focus ring appearance and CSS implementation, but does not address focus visible vs. focus semantics for keyboard-only users. The specification shows `outline: 2px solid` but doesn't clarify whether `:focus-visible` (keyboard/tab focus only) or `:focus` (all focus, including click) is the correct pseudo-class to use. This matters for accessibility: keyboard-only users need to see focus, but sighted mouse users may not want focus ring on click.</gap>
      <question>Add explicit guidance: "Use CSS `:focus-visible` pseudo-class (keyboard focus only) to show focus ring. Do NOT use `:focus` alone (which includes mouse clicks). This ensures keyboard-only users see focus, while mouse users get clean interaction. Polyfill: `:focus-visible { outline: 2px solid #0052A3; } :focus { outline: none; }`" This removes ambiguity for Phase 7 developers on when focus rings appear.</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

</interview_brief>