<interview_brief phase="7">
  <summary>23 should-improve items found across L2 (7), L3 (7), L4 (9) for Phase 7 deliverable.</summary>

  <topic_group source="L2 -- Domain Expert (Engineering Manager / Technical PM)">
    <topic id="SI-7-L2-1">
      <context>Checklist says "Email Service (for notifications): [ ] Resend account created (https://resend.com) OR SendGrid account created (https://sendgrid.com)" without stating Ocean Golf's choice. D5 would contain this decision, but it's not referenced.</context>
      <gap>Email service selection (Resend vs. SendGrid) is listed as required pre-build account but Phase 5 does not specify which one was selected for Ocean Golf, leaving the founder uncertain which one to set up.</gap>
      <question>State explicitly: "For Ocean Golf, Phase 5 selected [RESEND | SENDGRID] because [REASON: e.g., 'Resend is simpler for startup scale and integrates with Node.js']. Set up account at [EXACT URL]." If deferred to Phase 7, state "Email service selection deferred to Phase 7 card FC-075."</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-7-L2-2">
      <context>Template specifies: "Define three types of verification: Card-level, Integration, Milestone." The calendar lists Checkpoint 1, 2, etc., but does not show which days/times the founder needs to be present to test (Thursday morning sessions are listed separately). Merged calendar would be clearer.</context>
      <gap>The sprint calendar shows dates and card ranges but does not show which days are testing/verification gates vs. active build days, making it unclear when the founder should be available for testing (per template requirement: "Verification gates between card groups").</gap>
      <question>Add legend to sprint calendar showing: "Build days (Mon-Wed, dev team works): FC-001, FC-002, etc. | Founder testing day (Thu morning, 10:00-11:30 AM): Verify checkpoint criteria | Friday (cleanup + prep): Final verification, git commit, prep for next week." This aligns the calendar with the separate "Founder Testing Schedule" table.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-7-L2-3">
      <context>FC-001 through FC-007 have 15-20 line specifications with steps, acceptance criteria, git commit, and error scenarios. FC-008 onwards are 1-2 line bullets. Template requires: "every build card must be self-contained" and "a non-technical founder can verify it worked by following specific, observable acceptance criteria."</context>
      <gap>Cards FC-008 through FC-120 are specified in summary form ("FC-008: Create Booking_Courses junction table") but lack the detailed step-by-step, acceptance criteria, and error handling that cards FC-001 through FC-007 contain. This inconsistency violates the principle of "every card is self-contained."</gap>
      <question>Expand cards FC-008 through FC-120 to full specification format (matching FC-001 template) OR explicitly state in the header: "Cards FC-008 through FC-120 are specified in summary form in Section 5 due to length constraints. Full specification for each card will be generated during Phase 7 Card Specification Review (separate document). For now, card titles and dependencies are locked; details TBD." If full specs cannot fit in D8, reference a separate "D8-EXTENDED: Complete Card Specifications" document.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-7-L2-4">
      <context>Section 8 describes "Step 1: Re-run with context..." but does not show: "Example: FC-032 Send Reminder modal fails with 'Heroicons not found' error. Step 1 retry: Run `npm install @heroicons/react` and re-run. If fails again, Step 2: Break FC-032 into two cards (UI only, then integration)."</context>
      <gap>The error recovery protocol specifies three attempts (retry, simplify, different approach, then block) but does not provide concrete examples specific to Ocean Golf's build, making it hard for the founder to understand when/how to apply this to actual failures.</gap>
      <question>Add "CONCRETE EXAMPLE: Error Recovery in Action" subsection showing a realistic failure scenario (e.g., database migration timeout, API integration error, component rendering issue) and walking through all three recovery steps for that specific scenario. This makes the protocol concrete and applicable to actual build problems.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-7-L2-5">
      <context>Template says: "All of the following must be satisfied before Phase 7 is complete. You enforce this strictly." But there is no note stating who verified, when, and whether any criteria failed and were remediated before final approval.</context>
      <gap>The completion gate lists 38 checkboxes (all marked complete) but does not specify whether this gate was actually verified by an independent reviewer or is self-assessed by the D8 author. Template requires "independent verification" of gate criteria.</gap>
      <question>Add header to completion gate: "GATE VERIFICATION: Reviewed by [Name/Role] on [Date]. Status: [All criteria passed | N criteria failed, remediated, re-verified]. Sign-off: [Reviewer name, timestamp]." This provides auditability and shows the gate was not just self-checked but independently validated.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-7-L2-6">
      <context>Section says: "This is not the full Deliverable 9 — Phase 8 adds the intern-level step-by-step instructions..." but does not actually provide the structured credential sequencing data. D9 Phase 8 author will need to extract/rebuild this from D8 narrative, which violates "structured data handoff" principle.</context>
      <gap>D8 states it produces "Partial Deliverable 9 Input: Credential Sequencing Map" but does not provide the actual credential sequencing data structure (which services pre-build, during-build, post-build) for D9 to consume, only describes what D9 will contain.</gap>
      <question>Add explicit "Credential Sequencing Skeleton (For D9)" table in Phase Outputs section: | Service Name | Category (Pre/During/Post) | Setup Card | Environment Variables | Auth Method | Notes |. Fill this table with all services referenced in pre-build checklist, making it a direct input for D9 Phase 8 to elaborate into full guide.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-7-L2-7">
      <context>Section 9 lists card titles and milestones but provides no step-by-step instructions for these critical final cards. Template requires: "every build card must be self-contained" with "specific, observable acceptance criteria." These cards (production env setup, domain config, final verification) deserve equal detail to earlier cards.</context>
      <gap>Pre-launch cards (FC-105 through FC-120) are mentioned and their titles listed, but no detailed card specifications are provided (steps, acceptance criteria, error handling) unlike the fully specified cards FC-001 through FC-047 and the detailed outline for FC-048 onwards.</gap>
      <question>Expand "SECTION 9 — Pre-Launch Configuration Cards" to provide full card specifications for FC-105 through FC-120 (following the same format as FC-001 through FC-007), OR explicitly note: "Pre-launch cards FC-105 through FC-120 require full specification in D8-EXTENDED. Titles and dependencies are locked; detailed steps TBD in Phase 7 week 6."</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

  <topic_group source="L3 -- Downstream Consumer (DevOps Lead / Head of Infrastructure)">
    <topic id="SI-7-L3-1">
      <context>Gate "After Phase 2 (Database): Database is Connected Verification" lists checkboxes but says "Supabase dashboard shows all 12 tables — check manually in Table Editor" with no instruction for automating schema verification into the CI/CD pipeline.</context>
      <gap>Verification gates list (After Phase 1, After Phase 2, etc.) specifies WHAT to check but not HOW to automate these checks into CI/CD or who is responsible for running them. This creates ambiguity about whether founder manually verifies, or if checks are automated.</gap>
      <question>For each verification gate, add: "(1) Manual step: Founder opens dashboard and confirms X. (2) Automated step (if applicable): CI/CD runs [command/test] and passes before proceeding." If manual, state timeout (e.g., "Founder must verify within 1 hour of card completion or build pauses"). If automated, specify GitHub Actions job or test suite that validates gate."</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

</interview_brief>