<interview_brief phase="8">
  <summary>25 should-improve items found across L2 (10), L3 (8), L4 (7) for Phase 8 deliverable.</summary>

  <topic_group source="L2 -- Domain Expert (DevOps Lead / Head of Infrastructure)">
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-1">
      <context>`.env.local` template shows "`NEXT_PUBLIC_SUPABASE_ANON_KEY=eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9...`" without explaining it's a restricted token</context>
      <gap>The template shows `NEXT_PUBLIC_SUPABASE_ANON_KEY` as `eyJhbGciOiJIUzI1NiIsInR5cCI6IkpXVCJ9...` which is a JWT-style token, but doesn't explain what this is or why it's safe to be "public" (it's visible in browser), which could confuse founder about security.</gap>
      <question>Add a comment above the NEXT_PUBLIC variables: "NEXT_PUBLIC_* keys are visible in browser—these are restricted tokens, not your full database password. Your database is protected by Supabase RLS (Row Level Security) policies."</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-2">
      <context>D8 summary says "11 credentials" but lists 11 distinct accounts (some during-build); D9 executive summary says "Total accounts to create: 9 services + 1 registrar + hosting provider = 11 credentials"</context>
      <gap>D8 states "Total accounts to create: 9 services + 1 registrar + hosting provider = 11 credentials" but D9 lists 11 accounts (GitHub, Supabase, Stripe, Resend, Domain Registrar, Hosting, Password Manager, WhatsApp, Twilio, Google Analytics, Sentry), which is 11 total, not 11 non-hosting-provider accounts. Math doesn't match.</gap>
      <question>Clarify the count: separate pre-build accounts (immediate) from during-build accounts (FC-033, FC-075, etc.) so founder knows exactly how many to create before April 15. Update D8 Section 1 to match D9's accounting.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-3">
      <context>Tier 1 Hosting: "$5–20" with note "Railway charges for actual compute + storage used" but no link between usage patterns and cost</context>
      <gap>Cost projections for Hosting (Railway) show "$5-20" for Tier 1 and "$10-30" for Tier 2, but no explanation of what usage level triggers the cost. For a founder planning budget, "variable costs with wide range" is unhelpful without usage metrics (storage, bandwidth, compute minutes).</gap>
      <question>Add a worked example for each hosting tier: "Example Tier 1 usage: 1GB storage, 50GB bandwidth, 100 compute minutes = ~$10/month. Example Tier 2: 5GB storage, 300GB bandwidth, 500 compute minutes = ~$25/month." Founder can then estimate based on anticipated growth.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-4">
      <context>"□ Verify domain registration doesn't expire" appears as a single-line checklist item with no steps</context>
      <gap>D11's quarterly maintenance checklist refers to tasks like "Verify domain registration doesn't expire" but doesn't specify HOW to verify (e.g., "Log into registrar, check renewal date in dashboard, set up auto-renewal if available"). Instructions should be intern-level.</gap>
      <question>Expand quarterly checklist items to include step-by-step verification procedures at intern level, or cross-reference the relevant section in D9 that covers logging into the registrar.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-5">
      <context>"`api_logs` | ⚠️ PARTIALLY | ip_address, endpoint, response_code, timestamp`"</context>
      <gap>D12 includes a data inventory table cross-referencing D4 schema, but the table entries show "⚠️ PARTIALLY" for api_logs and audit_log without explaining which COLUMNS in those tables contain personal data or what makes them "partial."</gap>
      <question>Clarify the ⚠️ PARTIALLY entries: "api_logs contains ip_address (personal data per GDPR), but not user PII directly. For privacy purposes, treat as personal data." This helps lawyer understand the scope when reviewing D12.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-6">
      <context>"**FOUNDER CHOICE REQUIRED:** ☐ Option A (Ocean Golf owns booking data) ☐ Option B (User owns booking data)" with brief rationales but no legal risk disclosure</context>
      <gap>D13 presents content ownership as a binary choice (Users own vs. Ocean Golf owns) with examples, but doesn't explain the legal implications for Rafael—e.g., if users own content, Ocean Golf has indemnity risk if user content is inaccurate; if Ocean Golf owns content, can users be restricted from competing?</gap>
      <question>Add a "Legal Implications" subsection for each option before the founder decision gate, noting indemnity, IP, and competitive risks. Also note that lawyer (during legal review of D12/D13) should confirm this choice is sound.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-7">
      <context>Sprint 1 Week 3 (May 3) shows "Checkpoint 6 ✓ First action works" but doesn't flag that FC-032-035 may depend on Resend account being active, which requires founder to have created it (D9 C4 references it as pre-build).</context>
      <gap>D8 provides a detailed week-by-week calendar but doesn't account for "founder decision latency"—some cards may block until founder provides input (e.g., D12's content ownership choice, D13's dispute resolution preference). Calendar assumes decisions are made synchronously, but D9/D12/D13 suggest decisions are "pending."</gap>
      <question>Add a "Decision Gate Timeline" section showing which build cards are blocked by pending founder decisions (D12 Section 4 decisions, D13 Section 6 decision, etc.). Recommend decisions be finalized by April 1 at latest (2 weeks before build starts) to avoid timeline slip.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-8-L2-8">
      <context>"Post-Database Testing Instruction (Founder): After all 12 database tables are created: 1. Open Supabase dashboard 2. Run seed script: npm run seed (populates test data) 3. Verify seed data appears..."</context>
      <gap>Post-Database verification includes "Run seed script: npm run seed" but doesn't explain what the founder should do if seed fails (error messages, rollback steps). This is a potential blocker left unresolved.</gap>
      <question>Add error recovery: "If `npm run seed` fails with error 'foreign key violation,' re-check that all 12 tables were created (verify in Supabase Table Editor). If error persists, contact build team. If seed succeeds but data appears partial, re-run: `npm run seed:reset` and verify again."</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

</interview_brief>