<interview_brief phase="1">
  <summary>32 should-improve items found across L2 (11), L3 (8), L4 (13) for Phase 1 deliverable.</summary>

  <topic_group source="L2 -- Domain Expert (Co-founder / Strategic Advisor)">
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-1">
      <context>Section 1.4 lists four ecosystem elements (1–4) as parallel possibilities with no indication of which is most critical, which is nearest-term, or which enables others. The growth path (Section 4.2) mentions ecosystem partnerships in Stage 3 but does not reference the specific layers from Section 1.4, creating disconnect between vision and staged execution.</context>
      <gap>The "Ecosystem Potential" subsection describes four possible future layers (Venue Partnerships, Multi-Operator Licensing, Booking API, Loyalty Layer) but does not prioritize or sequence them, leaving ambiguity about the strategic order or relative importance.</gap>
      <question>Either: (a) Rank the four ecosystem layers by strategic importance (which creates defensibility, which drives revenue, which enables others), or (b) Explicitly map them to growth stages in Section 4.2 so a reader can see which ecosystem element is targeted in which stage. This clarification binds Phase 3 prioritization and Phase 7 sequencing.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-2">
      <context>Section 2.2 derives three separate TAM estimates: (1) $125M–$280M from golf tourism, (2) $2.4M–$19.2M from concierge spend, and (3) $5M–$25M from comparable services. The narrative then states "Ocean Golf's total addressable market (TAM) is estimated at **$5B–$25B**" — a figure that appears disconnected from the preceding calculations and lacks clear derivation. The stated $5B–$25B is a 5x range (compliant with template requirements) but the connection to the three layered calculations is not transparent.</context>
      <gap>The TAM calculation uses layered estimates from three sources but does not clearly reconcile the three resulting ranges into a single stated TAM figure, creating ambiguity about which range represents the final answer.</gap>
      <question>Clarify the TAM derivation by either: (a) Explaining how the three estimates rollup to the stated $5B–$25B, (b) Selecting one of the three methodologies as the primary TAM (e.g., "concierge services comparable market = $5M–$25M for Cabo globally, suggesting Ocean Golf TAM of $500M–$2.5B if expanded to all luxury golf destinations") and noting the others as validation, or (c) Presenting the $5B–$25B as a global luxury concierge TAM and then narrowing to Ocean Golf's realistic initial market of $900K–$4.5M (Los Cabos U.S. clients) as the near-term opportunity. Current presentation is confusing.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-3">
      <context>Stage 1 trigger: "When Rafael and Lucia have completed 50+ bookings..." (quantitative, clear). Stage 2 trigger: "When the platform has successfully handled 300+ distinct clients..." (quantitative, clear). Stage 3 trigger: "When Ocean Golf has successfully operationalized at least two of the three partnership types..." (qualitative, ambiguous — what does "successfully operationalized" mean? Revenue threshold? Booking volume?). Stage 4: "There is no subsequent stage with a single trigger condition" (explicitly deferred decision). This inconsistency could confuse Phase 9 monitoring of whether transitions are appropriate.</context>
      <gap>The trigger conditions for stage transitions are qualitative ("operational milestones are achieved") rather than quantitative, making it ambiguous when readiness for the next stage is confirmed.</gap>
      <question>For Stage 3 transition, define "successfully operationalized" with concrete metrics: e.g., "at least one venue partnership active with minimum 20 bookings per quarter routed through that partnership" or "white-label partnership signed with MOU specifying terms." For Stage 4, either define a trigger or explicitly state that Stage 4 is a decision point where Rafael chooses next direction (which is already stated but could be clearer). Ensure triggers are measurable by Phase 8/9.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-4">
      <context>Mitigation states: "Ocean Golf's defensibility is built on: (1) years of Rafael's personal relationships... (2) data assets... (3) white-glove positioning..." But the risk section (5.1) does not explain: What makes a multi-year relationship hard to poach? Can a competitor hire a respected course pro and build relationships in 18–24 months? How does the platform *specifically* make relationships harder to leave (e.g., through switching costs)? The mitigation is intuitive but not deeply reasoned.</context>
      <gap>The competitive risk mitigation relies on "relationship defensibility" but does not sufficiently explain what makes relationships defensible against a well-resourced competitor or how the platform strengthens that defensibility beyond "data assets become more valuable."</gap>
      <question>Deepen the competitive risk mitigation by: (a) Explaining what switching costs the platform creates for clients (e.g., historical data, preference profiles, trusted advisor continuity), (b) Explaining why course relationships are sticky (volume brings revenue, direct booking requires channel conflict), (c) Acknowledging what a competitor could do (hire a respected local expert, undercut pricing) and when that becomes a material threat (Year 2–3 if competitor has capital). This gives Phase 9 a clear monitoring framework.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-5">
      <context>Section 5.9 states: "The platform should NOT enable fully self-service booking without Rafael's input." But Section 1.2 and throughout the narrative, clients are described as browsing and selecting, suggesting visibility into the full inventory. This tension is not resolved. If clients can self-service 80% of the booking process, Rafael's service fee becomes harder to justify, particularly for price-sensitive segments. The mitigation (Section 5.9) proposes "Design the platform to reinforce the curation value" but does not specify what prevents self-service bookings given the platform's transparent course database.</context>
      <gap>The risk assumes clients pay for curation value, but the platform's design (Section 6.2 and 6.3) explicitly enables clients to see available courses, villas, and restaurants independently, which could undermine the curation positioning and pricing power.</gap>
      <question>Clarify in Phase 3 whether Ocean Golf's platform allows clients to independently book courses and villas (which commoditizes the service) or whether Rafael's approval/curation is a gating step (which maintains positioning). If clients can self-service, accept that pricing power is lower and differentiation is purely relationship-based. If Rafael gates all bookings, document that constraint in D2/D3 so Phase 6/7 design respects it. Current deliverable is ambiguous on this critical design decision.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-6">
      <context></context>
      <gap>The cost-to-serve calculation attributes ~1–2 hours to "course coordination" but does not distinguish between routine coordination (after platform launch) and relationship-building work that Rafael will continue to own; this conflates operational cost with strategic work that should not be assigned a per-booking cost.</gap>
      <question>Separate "course coordination" into: (1) transactional course management (confirmations, schedule changes, special requests) — these hours should decline sharply as the platform matures and Lucia owns them, estimated $5–10 per booking, and (2) relationship management and partnership development — these hours are strategic overhead, not cost-per-booking, and should be reported as annual fixed cost (Rafael's time dedicated to nurturing course relationships). This clarification improves the unit economics model's accuracy for Phase 5 cost modeling.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-7">
      <context>Section 6.3 calculates revenue and costs assuming 1,500 annual bookings (mature state) but the completion gate notes Rafael currently serves 180 clients and is targeting Stage 1 stability at ~100–150 clients during peak season (Oct 2026–Mar 2027). At 180 annual bookings, the unit economics math changes: revenue of $550 × 180 = $99K revenue vs. fixed costs for platform ($500–1K/month = $6–12K annually) plus variable costs of $120 × 180 = $21.6K. This yields much tighter (or negative) margins in Year 1. The deliverable does not acknowledge this cash flow and runway concern, which is material for Phase 5 implementation planning.</context>
      <gap>The narrative provides unit economics at "maturity" (1,500 bookings) but does not model the near-term economics for Year 1 (estimated 180–300 bookings), leaving ambiguity about whether the business is viable in the launch phase before scaling.</gap>
      <question>Add a "Near-term Year 1 Economics" paragraph showing: (1) Expected Year 1 booking volume (180–300), (2) Year 1 revenue at that volume, (3) Year 1 fixed + variable costs, (4) Resulting Year 1 profit/loss. Show how Year 1 operating revenue (or loss) flows into funding for Phase 2 development (D55-P1-011). This transparency helps Phase 8 operations planning and shows whether the bootstrap is viable or whether Rafael needs to maintain day job or secure pre-launch customer commitments.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-1-L2-8">
      <context>D55-P1-005 defines ambition as "sustainable growth business targeting $1.8M–$2.5M annual revenue... Rafael's ability to step back from operations while maintaining ownership." The final sentence acknowledges optionality ("acquisition possible, licensing possible, continued independence possible") but does not integrate this into the Platform Binds. This creates downstream ambiguity: Should Phase 5 architecture be designed to be acquirable (clean tech stack, minimal tech debt)? Should Phase 7 build for recurring revenue to increase valuation multiples? Should operations prioritize profitability or growth?</context>
      <gap>The ambition level entry states Ocean Golf is "lifestyle to growth hybrid" but does not explicitly address the founder's vision for eventual optionality (acquisition, licensing, continued independence); the binds field mentions "sustained state" but is unclear about what Phase 5 and 8 should do to preserve optionality.</gap>
      <question>Expand D55-P1-005 Constraint field to specify: "Platform should be designed to remain attractive as an independent business (profitability and operational efficiency prioritized) while not precluding acquisition or licensing partnerships. Phase 5 should use standard, maintainable technology that would transfer cleanly to another operator. Phase 8 should build operations that can be handed to a professional manager or acquisition team without critical-person dependency." This clarifies architectural and operational principles downstream.</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

</interview_brief>