<interview_brief phase="3">
  <summary>19 should-improve items found across L2 (5), L3 (6), L4 (8) for Phase 3 deliverable.</summary>

  <topic_group source="L2 -- Domain Expert (Product Manager / VP Product)">
    <topic id="SI-3-L2-1">
      <context>D3 Section 2.1 shows dependency chains in text format ("F-001 → F-002 → F-003 → F-008") and ASCII art, but no critical path analysis or build sequencing timeline. Phase 7 will need to know: "If course confirmation (F-006) takes 4 days to build, and it's on the critical path, then everything downstream (F-007, F-008, F-009) can't start until day 4. But payment processing (F-010) can be built in parallel." Without visualization, Phase 7 build scheduling is harder.</context>
      <gap>Dependency map (Section 2.1-2.3) is text-based and difficult to visualize. For a 12-feature MVP with parallelizable streams (course coordination in parallel with payment processing), a Gantt-style or graph visualization would clarify build sequencing for Phase 7.</gap>
      <question>Add phase visualization to Section 2: "Dependency graph shows critical path is F-004→F-005→F-006→F-007 (course confirmation bottleneck, 5-7 days estimated build time per Phase 7 estimates). Payment processing (F-010) and authentication are parallel-buildable (no dependencies). Itinerary (F-012) is last because it depends on confirmed courses + payment. Estimated build sequence: Week 1 (Auth + F-010 payment, Week 2 (F-004-F-007 courses), Week 3 (F-001-F-003 request flow + F-008-F-009 dashboards), Week 4 (F-012 itinerary + integration testing)." This preview of Phase 7 sequencing helps Phase 4 and 5 plan dependencies.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-3-L2-2">
      <context>D3 F-012 shows sample itinerary content and messaging ("Cabo Golf Experience - November 15-17, 2024") but does not specify: Layout (1-column, 2-column, card-based?), typography (font sizes, weights), color scheme (reference to luxury brands like Four Seasons or Virtuoso), whitespace rules, readability requirements (WCAG AA contrast?), mobile responsiveness (is it mobile-first?). Phase 6 will need these to design the template.</context>
      <gap>F-012 is described as "Beautiful, premium-looking itinerary" but lacks explicit UX/design requirements (layout, information architecture, visual style precedent) needed for Phase 6 design. The description is more lifestyle-focused than specification-focused.</gap>
      <question>Link F-012 to design precedent: "F-012 design inspiration: [Virtuoso client itinerary], [Four Seasons digital services], [Airbnb Experiences]. Design principles: premium minimal aesthetic, high whitespace, photography-forward, no transactional language (no price breakdowns, no 'booking engine' language). Phase 6 must create 2-3 design mockups of F-012 and get founder approval before building." This provides design direction without being overly prescriptive.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-3-L2-3">
      <context>D3 Section 10.1 allocates "Week 7-8: Testing & Refinement" but a 14-week plan with only 1-2 weeks of dedicated testing for 12 interconnected features seems aggressive. If bugs emerge during peak season (Oct 2026 when real bookings start), is there time to fix before volume increases? No buffer is documented.</context>
      <gap>Build sequence (Section 10.1) is week-by-week but does not account for: (a) testing and bug fix time (estimated at 20-30% of build time), (b) integration testing across features (F-006 confirmation email must integrate with F-008 booking record; no dedicated integration week), (c) Lucia and Rafael user acceptance testing (UAT), (d) course contact testing (actual course must test email confirmation workflow).</gap>
      <question>Adjust build timeline for realism: "Weeks 1-6: Core feature development (parallel streams as documented in Section 2). Weeks 7-8: Unit testing + bug fixes (estimated 1.5-2x estimated build time for bug-fixing). Weeks 9-10: Integration testing (verify course confirmation email + booking record + itinerary generation works end-to-end). Weeks 11-12: UAT with Lucia + Rafael (Lucia tests 5-10 sample bookings end-to-end, reports issues, Rafael signs off that platform meets operational needs). Weeks 13-14: Course contact testing + soft launch prep (Rafael calls 3-4 course contacts, they test email confirmation workflow with real requests, iterate if needed). Week 15 (Sept 1): Soft launch with 20-30 bookings during first 2 weeks; monitoring for bugs before full peak-season ramp." This extends timeline slightly but provides realistic buffer.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-3-L2-4">
      <context>D3 Section 11.4 lists Future Phase features as "F-001: Multi-Operator Platform Management" but Section 11.1 MVP has "F-001: Booking Request Form." If someone says "implement F-001," which F-001 is meant? Notation is confusing.</context>
      <gap>Feature registry in Section 11 uses notation system (F-###, G-###, E-###, F-###) where Future Phase features use "F-" prefix same as MVP features. This creates ambiguity in conversation: "F-001" is a Foundation/MVP feature, but "F-001" (future) is not. Consider renaming.</gap>
      <question>Rename Future Phase features to avoid collision: Use "FUT-001" or "X-001" for Future Phase instead of "F-###". Example: "FUT-001: Multi-Operator Platform Management" instead of "F-001: Multi-Operator Platform Management." This removes ambiguity and keeps registry unambiguous for all downstream phases.</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-3-L2-5">
      <context>D3 Section 7.1 analyzes GolfNow, GolfBreaks, CaboVillas.com, Questro Golf, Cabo Golf Deals. But the actual threat to Ocean Golf is internal to Rafael's relationships: if Carlos at Quivira decides "I'll offer villa packages + tee times directly and cut out Rafael," Ocean Golf's defensibility erodes. This risk is not surfaced in competitive analysis, though it's mentioned in D1 Risk Registry (D55-P1-009).</context>
      <gap>Competitive positioning table (Section 7.1) compares Ocean Golf favorably to GolfNow, GolfBreaks, etc., but does not address the most dangerous competitive threat: a founder's existing business relationship or an informal partnership. Example: what if a course contact or villa partner decides to offer concierge services directly to their clients (disintermediation)? This risk is not mentioned.</gap>
      <question>Add "Internal Partnership Risk" section to competitive analysis: "Disintermediation risk: Vendors (courses, villas, restaurants) may attempt to capture direct client relationships and offer concierge services independently, cutting out Ocean Golf commission. Mitigation: Ocean Golf's defensibility depends on serving clients better than any single vendor can. By coordinating multiple vendors (courses + villas + restaurants), Ocean Golf creates value that no single vendor can replicate. Over time, as Ocean Golf's data assets and personalization improve, switching costs increase. Short-term risk (Years 1-2): High if vendor relationships are transactional. Long-term defensibility (Years 3+): High if client relationships are sticky." This acknowledges the threat and frames how the platform mitigates it.</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

  <topic_group source="L3 -- Downstream Consumer (Senior Database Architect / Backend Lead)">
    <topic id="SI-3-L3-1">
      <context>Phase outputs state: "For each feature: unique identifier (e.g., F-001), name, description, module/category, user roles served, priority tier (MVP/Growth/Expansion/Future), estimated complexity (low/medium/high/very high), dependencies (references to other feature IDs), and data implications (what data this feature creates, reads, updates, or deletes)." Section 11.1 Feature Registry includes all fields for most features but omits explicit data implications for some. For example, F-007 (Confirmation Response Tracking) does not explicitly state "creates: confirmation_response record; reads: tee_time_request; updates: booking.status."</context>
      <gap>Phase outputs specify that each feature should include "data implications (what data this feature creates, reads, updates, or deletes)," but Section 11's Feature Registry does not consistently include this field for all features, making it harder for Phase 4 (Data Architecture) to derive entity requirements.</gap>
      <question>For each feature in Section 11 Feature Registry, add a "Data Implications" or "CRUD Operations" line explicitly stating what data objects the feature creates, reads, updates, or deletes. Example: "F-007: Confirmation Response Tracking | Data Implications: Creates confirmation_response records; reads tee_time_requests; updates booking.status; triggers notifications."</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-3-L3-2">
      <context>Section 11.1 describes F-008 as: "Single source of truth for every trip booking, storing all relevant data in one place." The narrative in Section 3.1 provides more detail (Booking Metadata, Trip Details, Course Confirmations, Vendor Details, Financial Tracking, Status & Workflow, Communication Log, Audit Trail) but the Feature Registry itself does not list these. Phase downstream consumers (Phase 4 Data Architecture) need this level of detail in the registry to design the schema.</context>
      <gap>F-008 (Unified Booking Record) description is vague about the actual data structure and fields stored, making it difficult for Phase 4 to understand what "single source of truth" operationally means in terms of data entities.</gap>
      <question>Expand F-008 description in Section 11.1 to include the main data categories it contains, or reference Section 3.1 explicitly. Example: "F-008: Unified Booking Record | Description: Central database record for each trip containing [see Section 3.1 Record Structure]: Booking Metadata, Trip Details, Course Confirmations, Vendor Details, Financial Tracking, Status & Workflow, Communication Log, Audit Trail."</question>
    </topic>
    <topic id="SI-3-L3-3">
      <context>Section 4.2 states: "As soon as Ocean Golf reaches 50+ concurrent bookings (estimated late October), these deferred features become essential: G-001 (Pre-Trip Reminders) — At 50 trips, manually reminding clients is 3+ hours of Lucia's week." This is one example, but other deferred features lack explicit trigger quantification. Phase 7 and Phase 8 need concrete metrics to determine "when to accelerate Phase 2 features into development."</context>
      <gap>Section 4.2 states that deferred features like G-001 (Pre-Trip Reminders) "will become critical in October" but does not quantify the trigger condition (e.g., "when concurrent bookings exceed 30" or "when Lucia's manual WhatsApp volume exceeds 5 hours/week").</gap>
      <question>For each Growth Phase feature (G-001 through G-011), add an explicit "Trigger Condition" line specifying the quantified metric that activates development. Example: "G-001: Pre-Trip Confirmations | Trigger: When concurrent bookings exceed 30 (estimated October 2026) OR when Lucia's manual communication load exceeds 10 hours/week." This gives Phase 7 and 8 objective milestones.</question>
    </topic>
  </topic_group>

</interview_brief>